restored316designs.com 2019-04-24

# Privacy Policy • Restored 316

BY VISITING RESTORED316DESIGNS.COM, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY.

#### OVERVIEW

RESTORED316 is committed to protecting your privacy online. This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we collect through this website at RESTORED316DESIGNS.COM (the “Site”), and how we collect and use that information.

The terms “we,” “us,” and “our” refers to RESTORED 316. The terms “user,” “you,” and “your” refer to site visitors, customers, and any other users of the site.

The term “personal information” is defined as information that you voluntarily provide to us that personally identifies you and/or your contact information, such as your name, phone number, and email address.

We provide WordPress themes in the form of a digital file, as well as customization and theme support (the “Service”).

Use of RESTORED 316, including all materials presented herein and all online services provided by RESTORED 316, is subject to the following Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all site visitors, customers, and all other users of the site. By using the Site or Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy, without modification, and acknowledge reading it.

#### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

This Site only collects the personal information you voluntarily1 provide to us, which  
may include:

  * First and Last Name
  * Email Address
  * Website URL
  * Login information for your Restored 316 account
  * Login information for your WordPress dashboard (used for theme support or customization services)

The information you provide is used to process transactions, send periodic emails, and improve the service we provide. We do share your information with trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business and servicing clients and visitors. These trusted third parties agree to keep this information confidential. Your personal information will never be shared with unrelated third parties.

#### ACTIVITY

We may record information relating to your use of the Site, such as the searches you undertake, the pages you view, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site.

#### COOKIES

We may send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the quality of our service. The term “cookies” refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the Site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). You have the ability to accept or decline cookies using your web browser settings. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly or at all.  The Site does not respond to Do Not Track signals sent by your browser.

#### THIRD PARTY LINKS

The Site may contain links to third party websites. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on our Site. Other sites accessible through our site via links or otherwise have their own policies in regard to privacy. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third parties.

#### SECURITY

We maintain security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, misuse, or disclosure. However, no exchange of data over the Internet can be guaranteed as 100% secure. While we make every effort to protect your personal information shared with us through our Site, you acknowledge that the personal information you voluntarily share with us through this Site could be accessed or tampered with by a third party. You agree that we are not responsible for any intercepted information shared through our Site without our knowledge or permission. Additionally, you release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of such intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

#### UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION

You may access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by logging into your account or by [emailing us](mailto:hello@restored316.com).

#### Visitors’ GDPR Rights

According to the GDPR a “data subject” is defined as an identifiable natural person. A natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as: a name, an identification number, location data, or online identifier. Alternatively, they may be identified by reference to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural, or social identity of that natural person. A data subject may be of any age or nationality.

As a data subject, within the European Union, you are entitled to certain rights under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Those rights include:

You have the right to be informed with respect to your personally identifiable information (PII) retained by the Company. As such, you may request access to your data that the Company stores and the rights to either correct or erase your personal data.

We will retain any personally identifiable information you choose to provide to us unless: (a) you request for us to delete the information, (b) we stop using our existing data providers, or (c) at Company’s discretion, we decide to remove the data.

You have the right to seek restrictions on the processing of your data.

You have the right to object to the processing of your data and the right to the portability of your data.

You have the right to withdraw consent provided to the Company concerning the processing of your personal data, as well as the right to withdraw that consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based upon consent that occurred prior to your withdrawal of consent.

You have the right to not be subjected to automated decision-making via pre-ticked boxes, additions to our email marketing lists and the like.

You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority that has jurisdiction over issues related to the General Data Protection Regulation.

We require only the information that is reasonably required to enter into a contract with you. We will not require you to provide consent for any unnecessary processing as a condition of entering into a contract with us by way of downloading a lead magnet, webinar, freebie or any other traditional list building methods.

#### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Site and this Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. We will notify you of any changes to this privacy policy by posting those changes on this page.

#### CONTACT

If you have questions about our privacy policy, please email us [here](http://restored316designs.com/contact/).

Updated: MAY 2018
